Die, all of you!
Is this the immortal?
Lei Long.
Between heaven and earth,
everything is intertwined with cause and effect.
You are drowned in past grudges,
blinded by the evil desires in your heart,
and acting recklessly on this land.
But do you know that
the karma you created
is not borne by you alone?
Those who care about you
are also silently suffering from this pain.
Those who care about me?
I, Lei Long,
in this world,
have long been a loner.
Where are those who care about me?
Your brother
has not yet reincarnated.
My brother?
Where is he?
Do you still remember
in the past,
when you were a shaman,
the mountain god you devoutly worshipped?
You should have fulfilled your duty as a priest,
using your body as a pact
to connect the realms and reach the gods,
protecting the peace of this land.
But you were bewitched by your inner demons
and slaughtered every living soul in the village.
Because of this grave mistake,
the mountain god was implicated
and stripped of his divine title.
For a hundred miles around,
there is no longer any divine protection.
Drought demons are wreaking havoc,
and floods are frequent.
People are displaced,
and the land is filled with grief and suffering.
Your brother,
to atone for your monstrous sins,
abandoned the path of reincarnation,
and with a wisp of a remnant soul,
incarnated as a mountain slave.
Enduring the punishment of lightning strikes
and the suffering of wind erosion,
he took upon himself all the illnesses and disasters
of millions of people.
Holding the rain-praying umbrella you left behind,
he guards the mountaintop day and night,
just to help you atone.
In his heart,
his brother...
He is not the
heinous monster people speak of.
He is still
the hero who keeps the region safe
by fighting for justice.
He continues the ending you left unfinished.
And what about you?
What are you doing?
Immortal,
please don't let my poor brother
suffer this ordeal anymore.
I'll take the blame for what I've done.
Let me take
full responsibility for this matter.
Everyone
has their own destiny.
His suffering for you
is his destined tribulation.
Saving him,
delivering him,
is saving yourself,
delivering yourself.
If you sincerely follow the right path,
are you not also delivering him?
What you should do
is entirely up to you.
Brother.
Brother,
I...
It's fine.
Brother,
there is so much suffering in the world.
Over the years,
I've seen too much
for far too long.
But the karma of all this suffering...
It will never change because of you and me.
Come with me.
Let's finish
what we started.
We will do it
together.
Immortal.
I am one of the Four Demons of Tumen,
Tu Luohua.
I have been looking for you.
You must...
You must be careful.
I have my own destiny.
Go.
Four Demons of Tumen.
Thank you, Master.
Thank you, Immortal. Thank you, Immortal. Thank you, Immortal.
The Immortal has appeared.
Thank you, Immortal.
I am not an immortal.
Don't thank me.
If you want to thank someone,
thank Feilu.
Why?
Now,
although the demons have been eliminated,
but in the future,
we do not know what risks there will be.
You should still
make yourselves stronger.
Thank you, Immortal.
Tonight,
I will stay here for the night.
I'll hit the road early tomorrow morning.
Sneaking around.
Come in.
What is it?
Master,
where are you going?
To sell medicine.
Where to?
None of your business.
Master,
why don't you
take me with you?
I want to join you
to uphold justice everywhere.
I told you,
I'm just a medicine seller.
Then I'll sell medicine with you.
I can be your servant.
Washing clothes, cooking,
I'm good at everything.
No.
Master.
I'm going to rest.
Kid,
close the door.
Immortal,
you saved us.
We can never repay you.
We gathered some dry rations overnight.
If you don't mind,
please accept them.
Please accept them.
Our meeting
is merely fate.
Since it is fate,
there's no need to be so polite.
You already have it hard enough.
Keep these things
for yourselves.
Immortal,
please accept this.
For such a great favor,
if we don't thank you,
we won't have peace of mind.
Please accept it.
Immortal,
please accept it.
Please accept it, Immortal.
Just consider it as buying my goods.
Distribute these peace amulets.
They will keep you safe and sound.
Thank you, immortal.
Thank you, immortal. Thank you, immortal.
Thank you.
Ping Jieqiang, Hai Hui.
Ping Jieqiang.